citysquares.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy | CitySquares

This web site, including the information collected on this web site, is owned by Citysquares™ Online, Inc. ("Citysquares"). Citysquares is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. Our goal is to provide a safe and secure user experience. We will strive to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein. As a convenience to our users, this web site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any other web site. This privacy policy applies solely to this web site. 

## Information About Citysquares Online, Inc. and Affiliate Visitors 

Citysquares Online, Inc. and its affiliates collect information about all of our users; such as what area users visit most frequently and what services and features users access the most. This data is only used to benefit the user. From this data we can determine what is most beneficial to the user and how we can better the user experience. We may share this data with our partners, but only so they too can understand our users. 

## Information About Citysquares

Citysquares collect information about our users; such as what area users visit most frequently and what services and features users access the most. This data is used to benefit the user. From this data we can determine what is most beneficial to the user and how we can better the user experience. We may share this data with our advertisers and business affiliates to better understand the needs of our users.

## Information About You 

Citysquares collects and stores the personal information provided by you to properly identify you as a user on this web site. The personal information collected from this web site is used for a variety of purposes including identification, registration, authentication, on-line transactions, and marketing. In some instances, such as when you enter a classifieds posting, create a profile, enter a contest or respond to a survey, we may ask for information including but not limited to: your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number. We may use this information to alert you of new products, new services or upcoming events. Your personal information is accessible to you and you may update your personal information by logging into your Citysquares web site profile.

## General Information Disclosure 

Except as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose information about visitors, guests or registered users of Citysquares to outside parties. There are circumstances under which we will disclose personal information, without notice to you. For example, if we are required to do so by law, a court order or if in our reasonable belief such disclosure is necessary. We do not sell or rent the personal information of the users of this web site. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our service, such as service announcements, administrative messages, or newsletters, which are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

If you decide to order a product or service from this web site, certain personal information will be needed to process and fill your order. Citysquares and/or its advertisers and business affiliates will need your name, mailing address, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number, and your credit card number to process your order. We use the services of outside companies, such as shipping companies, credit card processing companies, and event registration, to process and fulfill orders. We provide these companies with the information that they need to perform the service and they are not permitted to use personal information for other purposes. We may share all information collected on this web site, including personal information, with our advertisers and business affiliates.

If you are browsing this web site, reading or downloading information, we automatically collect information about your visit. The information we collect may include the Internet domain, IP address, browser, and operating system of the computer you are using to access this web site, the date and time you logged on, the pages you visited, and if you linked to or from another web site. This information is anonymous and does not identify you personally. We use this information to analyze trends, statistics, determine user movement and identify heavily used web pages, and to help us provide a better web site and better service. We may also share aggregated information about our users with our advertisers and business affiliates. The information that we share does not contain personal information that can identify an individual.

We may from time-to-time, offer users the opportunity to participate in web based events, surveys or contests, or send email newsletters. You will be able to opt-out from these emails at your own discretion. Joining CitySquares implies your opting in. Participation in a web-based event, survey or contest is completely voluntary. Information requested for a survey or contest may include personal information (such as name, address, and age group), and demographic information. Personal information collected from a survey or contest may be used to notify the user participating in the survey or contest or as described above. Personal information collected from certain web-based events is used by the event sponsor or organizer subject to their own privacy policy. Questions regarding the privacy policy of a web-based event should be directed to the event sponsor or organizer directly. 

## Cookies

To enhance your experience with our website, Citysquares uses a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering user names and passwords and preferences, tracking click streams, and for load balancing. Using cookies to track your visit to Citysquares, our web server logs the IP/Internet address of your computer. Cookies also can be used to determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site, pages of the site most frequently visited, and time and date of the visits. This information does not identify you personally. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on Citysqaures’ web site.

## Feedback 

Citysquares has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes property of Citysquares. We may use this feedback for marketing purposes or to contact you for further feedback.

## Children 

This web site does not contain content, products or services that are marketed to children. We are committed to observing applicable laws and requirements regarding child privacy such as the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parent's consent prior to giving personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of Citysquares, we encourage you to use web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. We also encourage you to participate in your child's experience with Citysquares.

## Privacy Policy Changes 

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about Citysquares’ privacy policy please write to us at Citysquares Online, Inc., 411A Highland Ave, Suite 368, Somerville, MA 02144. Attn: Privacy.

## General

This is the complete and exclusive agreement between Citysquares and you regarding this subject matter and supersedes all prior agreements and all communications, whether written or oral, between the parties. This agreement may be amended, changed, or revised by Citysquares. Any such amendment, change or revision will be posted on this web site by Citysquares. A waiver of any violation or failure to enforce any provision of this agreement by Citysquares shall not constitute a waiver of any rights with respect to this agreement. The validity, construction, interpretation, and performance of this agreement shall be governed and construed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, exclusive of its rules regarding conflicts of law. Any suit or cause of action with respect to this Agreement may only be brought in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. English shall be the governing language of this agreement. All terms and conditions of this agreement are severable. If any term or provision, or any portion thereof, of this agreement is held to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, the remaining portions shall not be affected. Section headings are intended for convenience only and shall not be used in the interpretation of this agreement. You agree any claim or cause of action you may have arising out of this agreement or related to any Citysquares service must be filed within one (1) year after the date of the damage, loss or injury giving rise to any such claim or cause of action or you will be forever barred. All other provisions of this agreement which by their nature may reasonably be interpreted to survive the expiration or termination of this agreement, shall survive any expiration or termination of this agreement.

Thank you for using Citysquares Online, Inc. 

Last revised 9/25/2007 2:48 PM.
